William Francis Gray Swann Papers 1903-1962 Mss.B.Sw1
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1916-1958; 3.0 Linear feet
  - Bethe, Hans A., 1937-1955; 5 items (Box 7)
  - Bevan, Arthur, 1939; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Biester, Dorothy, 1935; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Bilger, Leonora Neuffer, 1938; 3 items (Box 7)
  - Birkhoff, George D., 1936-1943; 7 items (Box 7)
  - Bishop, D. W., 1944; 3 items (Box 7)
  - Bitter, Francis, 1936-1939; 6 items (Box 7)
  - Bittinger, Charles, 1934-1941; 32 items (Box 7)
  - Blackburn, Harmon L., 1942; 3 items (Box 7)
  - Blackburn, Charles M., 1925; 1 items (Box 7)
  - Blackett, P. M. S., 1940; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Blackett, Patrick, 1956; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Blair, William B., 1921; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Blanchard, Frances, 1937; 3 items (Box 7)
  - Blanchard, Duncan, 1961; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Blau, Adi, 1933; 4 items (Box 7)
  - Blaxland, M., 1956, 1961; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Bleick, Willard E., 1929; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Bliss, Gilbert Ames, 1922-1937; 8 items (Box 7)
  - Bliven, Bruce, 1940; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Block, I. Edward, 1952; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Blodgett, Alice E., 1941-1942; 7 items (Box 7)
  - Bloom, Julius, 1943-1956; 9 items (Box 7)
  - Bludworth, T. Franklin, 1944-1955; 22 items (Box 7)
  - Boggs, S. Whittemore, 1940; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Bohr, Aage, 1957; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Bohr, Niels, 1934; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Bok, Bart J., 1941; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Bok, Mrs. Curtis, 1936; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Bok, Mary, 1939-1940; 7 items (Box 7)
  - Bolster, C. M., 1949-1952; 4 items (Box 7)
  - Bond, Kirk, 1953-1954; 7 items (Box 7)
  - Bond, R. T., 1937; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Bongards, H., 1923; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Bonner, T. W., 1940-1957; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Boocock, C. B., 1937; 3 items (Box 7)
  - Boott Mills, 1921; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Borie, Edith, n.d.; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Born, Max, 1937-1938; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Bostelmam, John C, Jr., 1935-1939; 32 items (Box 7)
  - Bouvet, Rene, 1941-1942; 4 items (Box 7)
  - Bouvier, Julian J., 1940; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Bowker, R. C., 1944; 5 items (Box 7)
  - Bowles, Gordon T., 1951; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Boyajian, A., 1936; 7 items (Box 7)
  - Boyd, George A., 1938-1941; 5 items (Box 7)
  - Bracking, Ivy A., 1940; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Bradbury, N., 1946; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Bradshaw, Hamilton, 1937-1939; 7 items (Box 7)
  - Bradt, Helmut L., 1947; 5 items (Box 7)
  - Bragg, Lawrence, 1954; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Bragg, William, 1940; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Brakeley, George A., 1937; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Bramhall, Ervin Hicks, 1933; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Bramley, Arthur, 1934; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Brammer, Douglas, 1957; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Bransfield, J. W., 1955; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Brasefield, Charles J., 1955; 1 item (Box 7)
  - Breisky, John V., 1938; 7 items (Box 7)
  - Breit, Gregory, 1924-1958; 19 item (Box 7)
  - Brennan, Herbert, 1925; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Brentano, J. C. M., 1942; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Brice, C. Frederick, 1938-1942; 6 items (Box 7)
  - Bridgman, P. W., 1923; 2 items (Box 7)
  - Briggs, H. B., 1929; 3 items (Box 7)
  - Briggs, Lyman J., 1934-1958; 5 folders (Box 7)
    - Folder 1, 1934 (Box 7)
    - Folder 2, 1935-1936 (Box 7)
    - Folder 3, 1945-1947 (Box 7)
    - Folder 4, 1948-1949 (Box 7)
    - Folder 5, 1950-1958 (Box 7)
  - Briggs, Sylvia Swann, 1940-42; 3 items (Box 8)
  - Brighton School of Music, 1928-1934; 11 items (Box 8)
  - Brinkworth, J. H., 1911; 3 items (Box 8)
  - Bronk, Detlev W., 1949; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Bronson, Howard L., 1928; 1 item (Box 8)
  - Brookhaven National Laboratory, n.d.; 1 item (Box 8)
  - Brown, F. C., 1937; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Brown, G. H., 1936; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Brown, Louis, 1953; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Brown, Marshal S., 1937; 9 items (Box 8)
  - Brown, Raymond Charles, 1942; 10 items (Box 8)
  - Broxon, James W., 1921-1934; 2 folders (Box 8)
    - Folder 1, 1921-1923 (Box 8)
    - Folder 2, 1927-1934 (Box 8)
  - Bryn Mawr College, 1939; 1 item (Box 8)
  - Buchta, J. W., 1936-1955; 2 folders (Box 8)
    - Folder 1, 1936-1939 (Box 8)
    - Folder 2, 1941-1955 (Box 8)
  - Buckingham, 1921, 1927; 3 items (Box 8)
  - Bunker, John W., 1940; 1 item (Box 8)
  - Burdick, C. Lalor, 1936; 3 items (Box 8)
  - Burgess Battery Company, 1935-1936; 13 items (Box 8)
  - Burkholder L. M., 1950; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Burlew, John S., 1955-1959; 32 items (Box 8)
  - Burns, George R., 1940; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Burroughs, Robert E., 1936; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Burton, Ernest D., 1924; 3 items (Box 8)
  - Bush, Vannevar, 1940-1942; 20 items (Box 8)
  - Bye, Arthur Edwin, 1929; 11 items (Box 8)
  - Byrd Antarctic Expedition II, 1933; 3 items (Box 8)
  - C. B. Christiansen Company, 1936; 8 items (Box 8)
  - Cady, Walter G., 1945; 12 items (Box 8)
  - Caldwell, Orestes H., 1933; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Calhoun, Phil, Maj., 1949; 2 items (Box 8)
    Flying saucers and use of light for propulsion
  - Callaghan, Thomas A., 1947; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Callendar, H. L., 1907-1924; 9 items (Box 8)
  - Camacho, Manuel Avila, 1943; 8 items (Box 8)
  - Cambridge Instrument Company, 1925; 1 item (Box 8)
  - Campbell, George A., 1932-1933; 9 items (Box 8)
  - Campbell, W. W., 1927; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Cancer Research Fund, 1929-1935; 5 folders (Box 8)
    - Folder 1, 1929 (Box 8)
    - Folder 2, 1930-1931 (Box 8)
    - Folder 3, 1932 (Box 8)
    - Folder 4, 1933-1934 (Box 8)
    - Folder 5, 1935 (Box 8)
  - Canfield, Jennings W., 1954; 2 items (Box 8)
  - Canova, E. C., 1947; 1 item (Box 8)
  - Cardoza, J. B. N., 1932; 4 items (Box 8)
  - Carnegie Institution of Washington, 1926-1951; 40 items (Box 8)
  - Carnegie Institution of Washington. Department of Terrestrial Magnetism, 1923; 7 items (Box 8)
  - Carp, Louis, 1955; 5 items (Box 9)
  - Carpenter, Samuel, 1952; 1 item (Box 9)
  - Carr, Fred, 1934; 4 items (Box 9)
    Re: James Jeans' view of the new physics
  - Carroll, C. M., 1943; 1 item (Box 9)
  - Carson, Cyril T., 1961; 2 items (Box 9)
  - Carter, Howard A., 1947; 19 items (Box 9)
  - Carter, Robert S., 1956; 2 items (Box 9)
  - Carter, W. J., 1936; 2 items (Box 9)
  - Casals, Pablo, 1947-1960; 64 items (Box 9)
  - Cassell, Norman S., 1922; 1 item (Box 9)
  - Castellini, William A. A., 1936; 2 items (Box 9)
  - Caster, Kenneth E., 1952; 3 items (Box 9)
  - Cattell, James McKeen, 1927-1943; 6 folders (Box 9)
    - Folder 1, 1927, 1936 (Box 9)
    - Folder 2, 1937-1939 (Box 9)
    - Folder 3, 1940 (Box 9)
    - Folder 4, 1941 (Box 9)
    - Folder 5, 1942 (Box 9)
    - Folder 6, 1943 (Box 9)
  - Cattell, Jacques, 1942; 3 folders (Box 9)
    - Folder 1, 1942 (Box 9)
    - Folder 2, 1943-1944 (Box 9)
    - Folder 3, 1945 (Box 9)
  - Cattell, Ware, 1939-1942; 20 items (Box 9)
  - Central Scientific Company, 1933; 2 items (Box 9)
  - Century of Progress, 1933; 4 items (Box 9)
  - Chalmers, Gordon K., 1937; 8 items (Box 9)
  - Chambers, Carl C., 1933-1951; 4 items (Box 9)
  - Chambers, Robert, Jr., 1951; 4 items (Box 9)
  - Chandrasekhar, Subrahmanyan, 1955; 2 items (Box 9)
  - Chapman, R., 1911; 1 item (Box 9)
  - Chapman and Grimes, Publishers, 1936; 2 items (Box 9)
  - Charlesby, A., 1957; 9 items (Box 9)
  - Charlton, William J., 1935; 2 items (Box 9)
  - Chase, Harry W., 1938; 3 items (Box 9)
  - Chatterjee, S. D., 1950-1958; 25 items (Box 9)
  - Cheyney, E. P., 1941; 3 items (Box 9)
  - Christian, L., 1925; 1 item (Box 9)
  - Civil Defense, 1950-1957; 16 folders (Box 9)
    - Folder 1, 1950 March-Oct. (Box 9)
    - Folder 2, 1950 Nov.-Dec. (Box 9)
    - Folder 3, 1951 Jan. (Box 9)
    - Folder 4, 1951 Feb (Box 10)
    - Folder 5, 1951 Mar. (Box 10)
    - Folder 6, 1951 Apr. (Box 10)
    - Folder 7, 1951 May (Box 10)
    - Folder 8, 1951 June (Box 10)
    - Folder 9, 1951 July (Box 10)
    - Folder 10, 1951 Aug. (Box 10)
    - Folder 11, 1951 Sept. (Box 10)
    - Folder 12, 1951 Oct. (Box 10)
    - Folder 13, 1951 Nov. (Box 10)
    - Folder 14, 1951 Dec. (Box 10)
    - Folder 15, 1952 (Box 10)
    - Folder 16, 1956-1957, n.d. (Box 10)
  - Clamer, G. H., 1945-1956; 7 folders (Box 10)
    - Folder 1, 1945-1946 (Box 10)
    - Folder 2, 1947-1948 (Box 10)
    - Folder 3, 1949 (Box 10)
    - Folder 4, 1950 (Box 10)
    - Folder 5, 1951-1953 (Box 10)
    - Folder 6, 1954-1955 (Box 10)
    - Folder 7, 1956 (Box 10)
  - Clancy, Edward P., n.d.; 1 item (Box 10)
  - Clark Cooper Company, 1946; 1 item (Box 10)
  - Clarke, Joseph R., 1914; 1 item (Box 10)
  - Clay, J., 1935-1949; 8 items (Box 10)
  - Clementson, M. K., 1946; 3 items (Box 10)
  - Clemons, Harry, 1942; 2 items (Box 10)
  - Clevenger, H. L., 1943; 1 item (Box 10)
  - Clevenger, S. J., Jr., 1943-1959; 6 folders (Box 11)
    - Folder 1, 1943 (Box 11)
      Franklin Institute
    - Folder 2, 1944 (Box 11)
    - Folder 3, 1945-1948 (Box 11)
    - Folder 4, 1949-1951 (Box 11)
    - Folder 5, 1952-1954 (Box 11)
    - Folder 6, 1955-1959 (Box 11)
  - Clews, M. Madison, 1949; 3 items (Box 11)
  - Cline, Mary, 1938; 3 items (Box 11)
  - Clinger, H., 1943; 1 item (Box 11)
  - Clipp, Roger W., 1954-1955; 5 items (Box 11)
  - Clothier, Isaac H., Jr., 1940; 1 item (Box 11)
  - Clothier, Morris L., 1939-1942; 6 items (Box 11)
  - Coade, E. N., 1924; 5 items (Box 11)
  - Coates, Joseph K., 1948-1956; 4 items (Box 11)
  - Cobbs, Susan P., 1958; 3 items (Box 11)
  - Coblentz, William Weber, 1951-1955; 3 items (Box 11)
  - Cockcroft, John D, 1956, 1960; 2 items (Box 11)
  - Coffey, W. C., 1942; 2 items (Box 11)
  - Coffin, L. A., 1956; 3 items (Box 11)
  - Coffin, Lewis G., 1948; 2 items (Box 11)
  - Coffman, L. D., 1921-1922; 9 items (Box 11)
  - Cohen, Leslie, 1953; 2 items (Box 11)
  - Cohen, Robert S., 1944; 1 item (Box 11)
  - Cohn, Byron E., 1949-1952; 12 items (Box 11)
  - Cohn, George I., 1956; 2 items (Box 11)
  - Colby, M. Y., 1949; 1 item (Box 11)
  - Cole, Leon Jacob, 1935; 1 item (Box 11)
  - Cole, Lois Dwight, 1937-1941; 5 items (Box 11)
  - Coleman, Warren, 1935; 3 items (Box 11)
  - Collie, C. N., 1957; 3 items (Box 11)
  - Collins, B. R. T., 1933; 2 items (Box 11)
  - Collins, George B., 1950; 1 item (Box 11)
  - Collins, Margaret W., 1946; 2 items (Box 11)
  - Collotype Company, 1947; 1 item (Box 11)
  - Colton, F. Barrows, 1949-1952; 3 items (Box 11)
  - Columbia Transcriptions, 1950-1958; 47 items (Box 11)
  - Columbia University, 1921-1928; 10 items (Box 11)
    Includes letters of Edward U. Condon, Bergen Davis, Frank D. Fackentha
  - Columbia University Press, 1943; 3 items (Box 11)
  - Colvin, Amy, 1944; 2 items (Box 11)
  - Comar, C. L., 1930; 2 items (Box 11)
  - Compton, Arthur H., 1933-1940; 3 folders (Box 11)
    - Folder 1, 1933-1936 (Box 11)
    - Folder 2, 1937-1938 (Box 11)
    - Folder 3, 1939-1940 (Box 11)
  - Compton, Karl T., 1924-1952; 3 folders (Box 11)
    - Folder 1, 1924-1934 (Box 11)
    - Folder 2, 1937-1942 (Box 11)
    - Folder 3, 1946-1952 (Box 11)
  - Conant, James B., 1940; 5 items (Box 11)
  - Conant, Lloyd V., 1958; 3 items (Box 11)
  - Condit, Carl W., 1953; 3 items (Box 11)
  - Condon, Eugene U., 1927-1952; 12 items (Box 11)
  - Conklin, Edward G., 1935-1942; 3 folders (Box 12)
    American Philosophical Society
    - Folder 1, 1935-1937 (Box 12)
    - Folder 2, 1938-1939 (Box 12)
    - Folder 3, 1940-1942 (Box 12)
  - Conley, Patrick, 1947; 5 items (Box 12)
  - Conrad, R. F., 11948; 3 items (Box 12)
  - Conrad, V., 1926; 3 items (Box 12)
  - Constantinides, Ph. A, 1925; 2 items (Box 12)
  - Contemporary Club (Philadelphia, Pa.), 1931; 2 items (Box 12)
  - Conway, Thomas F., 1946; 3 items (Box 12)
  - Cooke, James Francis, 1938; 4 items (Box 12)
  - Cooksey, Donald, 1959; 3 items (Box 12)
  - Coolidge, William D., 1934; 2 items (Box 12)
  - Corbett, Harriet Cumming, 1954-1957; 4 items (Box 12)
  - Cornell University, 1928-1931; 23 items (Box 12)
    Letters Of R. C. Gibbs, Harley Howe, Vladimir Karapetoff, E. H. Kennard, V. E. Peter
  - Coroniti, S. C., 1951-1952; 3 items (Box 12)
  - Corr, John E., 1956; 2 items (Box 12)
  - Correll, Malcolm, 1961; 2 items (Box 12)
  - Corson, Edward M., 1948-1957; 11 items (Box 12)
  - Corwin, Robert Nelson, 1924; 1 item (Box 12)
  - Cosinuke, Walter, 1943-1946; 5 items (Box 12)
  - Coulson, Thomas, 1946-1953; 5 items (Box 12)
  - Courtney, Pratt, J. S., 1957; 9 items (Box 12)
  - Cowie, Dean, 1933-1935; 11 items (Box 12)
  - Cox, Richard T., 1946-1949; 2 items (Box 12)
  - Crane, A, H., 1958; 1 item (Box 12)
  - "Crank" Letters, 5 folders (Box 12)
  - Crenshaw, J. L., 1933; 4 items (Box 12)
  - Crew, Henry, 1920-1950; 26 items (Box 12)
  - Crew, William H., 1945; 5 items (Box 12)
  - Crittenden, Miss, 1 item (Box 12)
  - Cross, Wilbur L., 1925-1938; 8 items (Box 12)
  - Culler, Vaughan, 1955; 2 items (Box 12)
  - Cummer, Frederick G., 1926-1936; 2 folders (Box 12)
    - Folder 1, 1926-1933 (Box 12)
      Mortgage to W.F.G. and Mabel Swann
    - Folder 2, 1934-1936 (Box 12)
  - Cummings, William, 1934; 1 item (Box 13)
  - Culp, Harvey W., 1953-1954; 8 items (Box 13)
  - Current Research, 1951; 2 items (Box 13)
  - Cyclotron Specialties Corporation, 1946; 1 item (Box 13)
  - Czerlinski, George, 1958; 2 items (Box 13)
  - Dahl, G. C., 1933; 1 item (Box 13)
  - Dalley, Florence Bartol, 1959; 4 items (Box 13)
  - Danforth, John L., 1943-1946; 36 items (Box 13)
    MIT
  - Danforth, William E., 1932-1959; 6 folders (Box 13)
    - Folder 1, 1932-1937 (Box 13)
    - Folder 2, 1938-1946 (Box 13)
    - Folder 3, 1947-1951 (Box 13)
    - Folder 4, 1952 (Box 13)
    - Folder 5, 1953-1954 (Box 13)
    - Folder 6, 1955-1959 (Box 13)
  - Darby, Hugh Hackland, 1932-1934; 16 items (Box 13)
  - Darling, Hugo, 1936; 1 item (Box 13)
  - Darrow, Karl K., 1925-1959; 5 folders (Box 13)
    - Folder 1, 1925-1935 (Box 13)
    - Folder 2, 1941-1942 (Box 13)
    - Folder 3, 1943-1949 (Box 13)
    - Folder 4, 1950-1952 (Box 13)
    - Folder 5, 1953-1959 (Box 13)
  - Dashman, Saul, 1924-1925; 5 items (Box 13)
  - Davey, Wheeler, P., 1934-1938; 3 items (Box 13)
  - Davies, C. E., 1924; 3 items (Box 13)
  - Davies, Lawrence E., 1936; 1 item (Box 13)
  - Davies, W. T., 1945-1946; 7 items (Box 13)
  - Davis, Charles C., 1947; 2 items (Box 13)
  - Davis, Don, 1957; 3 items (Box 13)
  - Davis, R. R., 1951; 4 items (Box 13)
  - Davis, Watson, 1937-1952; 6 items (Box 13)
  - Davisson, C. J., 1935; 2 items (Box 13)
  - Dawes, Rufurt, 1931; 1 item (Box 13)
  - Dawson, D. H., 1951; 1 item (Box 13)
  - Day, Arthur L., 1925-1948; 15 items (Box 13)
  - Dayton, 1958; 1 item (Box 13)
  - De Baldo, Jackie, 1957; 2 items (Box 13)
  - De Benedetti, Sergio, 1953-1959; 4 items (Box 13)
  - De Branges, Louis, 1959; 3 items (Box 13)
  - Debye, Pierre, 1925-1942; 14 items (Box 13)
    Re: Ehrenhaft, Einstein
  - Dee, Philip Ivor, 1954; 1 item (Box 13)
  - Dees, Bowen C., 1954; 1 item (Box 13)
  - Defense work, 1942; 1 item (Box 13)
  - Delaplaine, Mrs. Roy, 1957; 1 item (Box 13)
  - Delaware County Institute of Science, 1933; 2 items (Box 13)
  - Delbridge, 1942; 2 items (Box 13)
  - Del Rosario, C., 1929-1932; 11 items (Box 13)
  - Demaray, A. E., 1951; 2 items (Box 13)
  - Demos, Peter T., 1958; 6 items (Box 14)
  - Denniston, George C., 1943-1944; 2 items (Box 14)
  - Dent, Fred R., 194-1947; 3 items (Box 14)
  - Denver University, n.d.; 1 item (Box 14)
  - Dercum, Francis X., 1930; 1 item (Box 14)
  - Derge, G., 1950; 3 items (Box 14)
  - Derr, J. S., 1947; 3 items (Box 14)
  - DeSoto, Clinton B., 1946; 3 items (Box 14)
  - Deutsch, A, 1956; 1 item (Box 14)
  - Devons, S., 1954; 3 item (Box 14)
  - Dickerson, J. S., 1922-1924; 5 items (Box 14)
  - Diedrichs, Helene, 1930-1932; 17 items (Box 14)
  - Diesen, J. E., 1920; 1 item (Box 14)
  - Diesendruck, Leo, 1949; 2 items (Box 14)
  - Dike, P. H., 1943; 3 items (Box 14)
  - Dikeman, Esther, 1926; 1 item (Box 14)
  - Di Lauro, G. D., 1933; 4 items (Box 14)
  - Disque, R. C., 1937-1940; 4 items (Box 14)
  - Distillation Products Corporation, 1946; 1 item (Box 14)
  - Ditman, Norman E., 1934-1935; 2 items (Box 14)
  - Dodge, Homer L., 1930; 2 items (Box 14)
  - Dolan, Patrick, 1961; 1 item (Box 14)
  - Dolman, John, Jr., 1950; 1 item (Box 14)
  - Donnelly, Warren H., 1957; 1 item (Box 14)
  - Donohue, T. J., 1950; 1 item (Box 14)
  - Dorfman, A. E., 1958; 2 items (Box 14)
  - Dorsey, N. Ernest, 1927; 2 items (Box 14)
  - Doty, Edward A, 1948; 1 item (Box 14)
  - Doughton, Robert L., 1949; 1 item (Box 14)
  - Dover Publications, 1944-1946; 6 items (Box 14)
  - Downey, K. Melvina, 1928-1929; 2 items (Box 14)
  - Drake, Raleigh M., 1951; 5 items (Box 14)
  - Draper, C. H., 1904-1906; 2 items (Box 14)
  - Draper, Glen H., 1932-1935; 12 items (Box 14)
  - Dresden, Arnold, 1929-1936; 3 items (Box 14)
  - Drexel Institute of Technology, 1951; 2 items (Box 14)
  - Driscoll, Robert, 1959; 1 item (Box 14)
  - Dropkine, J., 1955; 4 items (Box 14)
  - Drury, Newton B., 1951; 1 item (Box 14)
  - Ducasse, C. J., 1957; 2 items (Box 14)
  - Dudley, Major, 1956; 2 items (Box 14)
  - Dudley, H. C., 1961; 4 items (Box 14)
  - Duff, E. E., 1946; 1 item (Box 14)
  - Duffield, Thomas J., 1929; 3 items (Box 14)
  - Duncan, George, 1960-1961; 2 items (Box 14)
  - Dunham, Franklin, 1934; 5 items (Box 14)
  - Dunnington, F. G., 1947; 2 items (Box 14)
  - Dun (?), Herbert, 1960; 1 item (Box 14)
  - DuPont, E. F., 1927; 3 items (Box 14)
  - DuPont, Mrs. E. Paul, 1937; 3 items (Box 14)
  - DuPont, Mrs. Irenee, 1937-1938; 12 items (Box 14)
  - DuPont DeNemours (E. I.) & Co., 1950; 2 items (Box 14)
  - Durrett, J. J., 1945; 7 items (Box 14)
  - Dwight, C. Harrison, 1924-1952; 12 items (Box 14)
  - Dyett, Edmond G., 1956; 2 items (Box 14)
  - Eachus, Iredell, Jr., 1956; 1 item (Box 14)
  - Eagan, Frances P., 1961; 3 items (Box 14)
  - Earnshaw, Thomas M., 1961; 2 items (Box 14)
  - Eastman Kodak Company, 1934-1935; 16 items (Box 14)
  - Eaton, J. A., 1935; 2 items (Box 14)
  - Eaton, Wayne G., 1943; 6 items (Box 14)
  - Eddington, Arthur, 1929-1942; 7 items (Box 14)
  - Edquist, E. L., 1947-1948; 2 items (Box 14)
  - Edwards, G. W., 1925-1926; 4 items (Box 14)
  - Edwards, Harry, 1944-1948; 3 items (Box 14)
  - Egerton, Alfred C., 1946; 2 items (Box 14)
  - Eggers, F. B., 1948; 2 items (Box 14)
  - Eglin, William C. L., 1925; 1 item (Box 14)
  - Egner, Russell Forrest, 1960; 3 items (Box 14)
  - Ehmert, A., 1955; 1 item (Box 14)
  - Ehrenfest, Paul, 1926-1931 (Box 14)
  - Ehrenhaft, Felix, 1938-1944; 3 folders (Box 14)
    - Folder 1, 1938-1940 (Box 14)
    - Folder 2, 1941 (Box 14)
    - Folder 3, 1942-1944 (Box 14)
  - Eicher, Edward C., 1937; 3 items (Box 14)
  - Eichler, Eugene, 1956; 3 items (Box 14)
  - Einstein, Albert, 1933-1950; 30 items (Box 14)
    Re: Ehrenfest, atomic bomb, special relativity
  - Eirich, Frederick, 1953-1954; 4 items (Box 15)
  - Eisenberg, Maurice, 1943-1960; 3 folders (Box 15)
    - Folder 1, 1943-1945 (Box 15)
    - Folder 2, 1946-1950 (Box 15)
    - Folder 3, 1951-1960 (Box 15)
  - Eisenhart, Luther P., 1927-1956; 6 folders (Box 15)
    - Folder 1, 1927-1928 (Box 15)
    - Folder 2, 1943 (Box 15)
    - Folder 3, 1945 (Box 15)
    - Folder 4, 1946 (Box 15)
    - Folder 5, 1947-1948 (Box 15)
    - Folder 6, 1949-1956 (Box 15)
  - Eisler, Adolf, 1934; 6 items (Box 15)
  - Eksergian, Rupen, 1932-1953; 7 items (Box 15)
    Comments on fire control, etc.
  - Eliot, Frederick M., 1921-1922; 3 items (Box 15)
  - Elliott, Carl F., 1945; 10 items (Box 15)
  - Elliott, E. C., 1935; 1 item (Box 15)
  - Elliott, Kathleen O., 1949; 2 items (Box 15)
  - Ellis, Weldon T., 1961; 22 items (Box 15)
  - Elman, Mischa, 1945-56; 6 items (Box 15)
  - Emanuel, Myron, 1948; 15 items (Box 15)
    Swann biography
  - Emberson, Richard M., 1948; 3 items (Box 15)
  - Embrey, L. A., 1943; 2 items (Box 15)
  - Emig, Catherine, 1939-1941; 2 folders (Box 15)
    - Folder 1, 1939-1940 (Box 15)
    - Folder 2, 1941 (Box 15)
  - Encyclopaedia Britannica, 1928-1929 (Box 15)
  - Enerson, Alfred, 1960; 1 item (Box 15)
  - Engel, A. Von, 1954; 2 items (Box 15)
  - Epstein, Paul S., 1926; 1 item (Box 15)
    Re: O.E. Frivold
  - Erikson, Henry A., 1917-1947; 4 folders (Box 15)
    - Folder 1, 1917-1918 (Box 15)
    - Folder 2, 1922-1924 (Box 15)
    - Folder 3, 1925-1928 (Box 15)
    - Folder 4, 1935-1947 (Box 15)
  - Erro, Luis Enrique, 1943; 2 items (Box 16)
  - Eurich, Alvin C., 1940; 3 items (Box 16)
  - Evans, Henry S., 1950-1954; 7 items (Box 16)
  - Evans, Ifor, 1956; 3 items (Box 16)
  - Evans, Robley, 1935-1938; 4 items (Box 16)
  - Eve, A. S., 1923; 1 item (Box 16)
  - Everett, Robert, 1955; 2 items (Box 16)
  - Exman, Eugene, 1956-1958; 6 items (Box 16)
  - Fahr, Sophia Lyon, 1960; 4 items (Box 16)
  - Fairchild, Milton, 1931; 4 items (Box 16)
  - Fairchild Engine and Airplane Co., 1949; 2 items (Box 16)
  - Falk, Charles E., 1950-1958; 9 items (Box 16)
  - Falmouth, Lord, 1956-1958; 8 items (Box 16)
  - Fan Mail -- "Is the Universe Planned?", 1953; 55 items (Box 16)
  - Fang, P. H., 1954; 6 items (Box 16)
  - Fardells, Messrs., 1940-1948; 36 items (Box 16)
    Re: house insurance (includes heavily censored letter)
  - Faris, Marvil L., 1943; 2 items (Box 16)
  - Farnsworth, R. L., 1946; 2 items (Box 16)
  - Fassin, Gustave, 1934; 9 items (Box 16)
  - Faucett, C. D., 1937; 1 item (Box 16)
  - Fawcett, C. C., n.d.; 2 items (Box 16)
  - Federation of American Scientists. Committee on Secrecy and Clearance, 1947; 2 items (Box 16)
  - Federer, Charles A., Jr., 1943-1955; 5 folders (Box 16)
    - Folder 1, 1943 (Box 16)
    - Folder 2, 1944-1951 (Box 16)
    - Folder 3, 1953 (Box 16)
    - Folder 4, 1954 (Box 16)
    - Folder 5, 1955 (Box 16)
  - Fekete, Zoltan, 1946-1948; 45 items (Box 16)
  - Fermi, Enrico, 1940-1953; 6 items (Box 16)
  - Ferry, Katherine, 1937; 4 items (Box 16)
  - Fidelity-Philadelphia Trust Company, 1928-1939; 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Folder 1, 1928-1933 (Box 16)
    - Folder 2, 1934-1939 (Box 16)
  - Field Joan, 1954; 5 items (Box 16)
  - Field, Richard M., 1953-1955; 8 items (Box 16)
  - Findlay, D. M., 1936; 1 item (Box 16)
  - Fink, George A., 1951; 2 items (Box 16)
  - Finkelstein, R., 1948; 8 items (Box 16)
  - First Federal Savings and Loan Association (Upper Darby, Pa.), 1950-1955; 22 items (Box 16)
  - Fisher, Edgar J., 1946; 10 items (Box 16)
  - Fisher, Franklin L., 1944; 4 items (Box 16)
  - Fisher, Irving, 1927; 2 items (Box 16)
  - Fisher, Raymond C., 1931; 1 item (Box 16)
  - Fisk, J. B., 1947-1948; 3 items (Box 16)
  - Fitzgerald, Edwin R., 1958; 3 items (Box 16)
  - Fleisher, Edwin A., 1936; 4 items (Box 17)
  - Fleming, John A., 1921-1936; 15 items (Box 17)
  - Fletcher, Angus, 1942; 9 items (Box 17)
  - Fletcher, Harvey, 1945; 1 item (Box 17)
  - Flowers, B. H., 1957; 3 items (Box 17)
  - Fogg, John M. Jr., 1958; 2 items (Box 17)
  - Foley, Francis, 1948-1949; 8 items (Box 17)
  - Follos, V., 1936-1937; 6 items (Box 17)
  - Foote, Paul D., 1925-194; 36 items (Box 17)
  - Forbes Stephen, 1949-1952; 9 items (Box 17)
  - Forbush, Scott B., 1947-1957; 21 items (Box 17)
  - Ford, Guy Stanton, 1922-1953; 5 items (Box 17)
  - Ford, Henry, 1934; 4 items (Box 17)
  - Forsythe, W. E., 19491950; 5 items (Box 17)
  - Fortescue, Richard L., n.d. (Box 17)
  - Fortune, W. C., 1955; 1 item (Box 17)
  - Fortune Magazine, 1948; 2 items (Box 17)
  - Foster, Duncan G., 1952; 1 item (Box 17)
  - Foster, J. S., 1931; 2 items (Box 17)
  - Foulke, Jeanne Kane, 1937; 1 item (Box 17)
  - Foulke, Willing B., 1942; 1 item (Box 17)
  - Fow, B. Richard, 1960; 9 items (Box 17)
  - Fowler, Marion W., 1926; 1 item (Box 17)
  - Fowler, William A., 1957; 4 items (Box 17)
  - Fox, Arthur L., 1932; 2 items (Box 17)
  - Fraenckel, Victor H., 1932; 2 items (Box 17)
  - Franck, J., 1938; 2 items (Box 17)
  - Frank, Adam, 1945; 1 item (Box 17)
  - Frank, Andrew, 1949; 4 items (Box 17)
  - Frank, Marco, 1948; 3 items (Box 17)
  - Frank, Philip G., 1941; 3 items (Box 17)
  - Frankford Arsenal -- Final Report, Armor, 1941 Sept.; 1 item (Box 17)
  - Franklin, Neil S., 1937-1938; 4 items (Box 17)
  - Franklin Institute, 1934; 41 items (Box 17)